<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SVSU Computer Science</string>
    <string name="action_main">Department Page</string>
    <string name="action_faculty">Faculty List</string>
    <string name="action_courses">Course List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faculty">FacultyActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_course_grid">CourseGridActivity</string>

    <string name="main_title_description">You’ll find SVSU’s Department of Computer Science &amp;
        Information Systems is staffed by qualified, competent professionals who are committed
        to teaching and research. We are here to help you grow and succeed in your academic and
        professional career. Our class sizes are small compared to other institutions and you’ll
        get to know and work with the CSIS faculty one-on-one. This helps to foster a learning
        environment aimed at student success.</string>
    <string name="mission_text">The mission of the Department of Computer Science and
        Information Systems at SVSU is to provide an outstanding education to its students
        in accordance with the guidelines of the SVSU mission, to advance scholarship in the
        key domains of the computing and information systems sciences, and to engage in activities
        that improve the welfare of society and enhance the reputation of SVSU.</string>

    <string-array name="faculty_array">
        <item>Il-Hyung Cho</item>
        <item>Moe Bidgoli</item>
        <item>George Corser</item>
        <item>Poonam Dharam</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="cho">Il-Hyung Cho\nAssociate Professor of Computer Science &amp; Information Systems\nDepartment of Computer Science and Information Systems</string>
    <string name="cho_bio">Il-Hyung Cho is an associate professor and chair of the Department of Computer
        Science at Saginaw Valley State University, Michigan, where he has been since 2003. During
        2010-2011 he was a Visiting Professor of Bioinformatics lab at Washington State University. He
        received a B.E. in Electronic &amp; Computer Engineering from Yonsei University in 1987, and an M.S.
        in Computer Science from Bowling Green State University. He received his Ph.D. in Computer Science
        from Clemson University in 2000. He worked at Iona Technologies in Boston as a software engineer in
        2000-2001, and at Clemson University as visiting lecturer in 2001-2003. </string>

    <string name="bidgoli">Moe Bidgoli\nAssociate Professor of Computer Science &amp; Information Systems\nDepartment of Computer Science and Information Systems</string>
    <string name="bidgoli_bio">Education:"\nMaster of Science, Univ Nebraska-Lincoln</string>

    <string name="corser">George Corser\nAssistant Professor of Computer Science &amp; Information Systems\nDepartment of Computer Science and Information Systems</string>
    <string name="corser_bio">Corser is a leader and advisor in a range of professional service activities.
        He is Organizer of TEDxSVSU and the faculty advisor of the student organization which coordinates
        TED Talks on SVSU campus. He is the Secretary of the Board of Directors of Early Career Academy, a
        Michigan charter public high school. He is a member of the ACM, SAE, IEEE Vehicular Technology Society,
        and the Michigan Infragard, a cyber security partnership between the FBI and the private sector, serving
        as a resource on the topic of digital security in the transportation sector. Corser is very active in
        promoting computer science education throughout SVSU and its surrounding community, leading the Hour of
        Code, serving as a Dow Corning faculty mentor and an AH Nickless mentor, and helping campus organizations
        develop web sites and mobile apps.</string>

    <string name="dharam">Poonam Dharam\nAssistant Professor of Computer Science &amp; Information Systems\nDepartment of Computer Science and Information Systems</string>
    <string name="dharam_bio">Education:\nDoctor of Philosophy, Universirty Memphis</string>

</resources>
